Now, we have the finished product, the triangle top that we started off with and then the bottom.
What's neat about the bottom is that it does have this band here that goes all the way around.
The band is just a little bit something that's different, and it also helps your suit stay on as well.
Here, we did no jewelry on the piece, but you could put on maybe a ring or something dangling from either side that you like, and also from the top if you wanted something extra as well.
So this is the finished product that we have.
You saw us make it.
You saw us with the--first, making the design of the suit, making the pattern, picking out your fabric, and then starting to sew it.
And with this suit, we did decide to do the elastic.
Elastic just kind of brings the suit a little bit more closer to the body.
It gives it a better fit, but this is optional, but it does look well on her body in this suit.
Also another thing to keep in mind, the padding in the top and the lining is completely optional as well, but it does give your suit more of a fitting and a longer-lasting, especially if you have the lining in it, it does give your suit longer wear to it, and if you accidentally do machine wash, it will be probably fine.
So there's a couple of things in this suit that you can change.
There's a couple of things you can make.
The band may be wider; also on the top, you can trim it in different colors; maybe the pink would look really great in this suit as well.
So once you get your pattern, you can always tweak it after your final product as well.
All you have to do is you're just going to take out something you don't like and put something into the suit, so it's up to you.
In conclusion, you've seen us start from scratch, from building a pattern and making a pattern into the finished product.
What might be a good idea is you to go out to the store and buy some fabric, maybe is not very expensive.
Just buy the cheapest you can do to practice.
That's the key here.
To make a good suit, you're going to need to practice.
So if you do buy just the cheaper material, practice into it, and then once you figure out, "Okay, well, I need to alter it this way," you can go back to your pattern and alter it.
So there are steps like that that you can do to make a good suit.
You've seen it and then you can do it.
It's very simple.
It's very fun doing it, and all you have to do is just the follow the steps to it.
And then once you have figured out your perfect pattern and everything, you can go out to the store, buy the fabric that you want and make it into something wonderful.